Anders G. Nordby



KEY COMPETENCIES

(+47) 932 20 333

anders@delichon.no

Processes

C

 \leq

Systems Architecture, Scrum, Kanban, Project Management.

https://www.linkedin.com/in/agnordby/

Updated version of this dokument:

https://github.com/agnordby/cv Barcelona (One week pr month in Oslo)

Development

C#, Akka.Net, GraphQL, NHibernate, Blazor, Gherkin, Specflow, Cypress, NUnit, Moq, Kiuwan, PowerBI, log4net, Episerver, ASP.Net, SQL, Javascript, NServiceBus, REST, Powershell, LATEX.

Tools

Jira, Confluence, TeamCity, Octopus Deploy, Git, TFS, SubVersion, NewRelic, jMeter, BlazeMeter, NuGet, Kiuwan.

CERTIFICATIONS

2021 Certified Optimizely Developer

2020 Microsoft AZ900 Azure Fundamentals

PRINCE2 Practitioner
Certified Scrum Master

2018 PRINCE2 Foundation

COURSES

2024 Building an AppSec Scanning Programme

2019 Tom Gilb: Architecture Workshop

2018 Sopra Steria: Arkitekturskolen

2015 Microsoft: Lead Enterprise Architect Programme

EDUCATION

2003 – 2004 University of Oslo, Teacher Training
 1999 – 2000 Oslo Business Academy, IT Candidate
 1987 – 1996 University of Oslo, Cand.Mag.
 1984 – 1987 Eikeli High School, Natural Sciences

AWARDS

2013-2017 Episerver Most Valued Professional

LANGUAGES

EXCELLENT Norwegian (native), English
INTERMEDIATE Bulgarian, German
BEGINNER Spanish, Japanese

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Systems Architect and Senior Developer with 20+ years of experience designing scalable software solutions across industries. Specialized in application security, distributed systems, and modern architecture. Proven leader in team coordination, agile practices, and security governance.

WORK EXPERIENCE

05/2019 – PRESENT

Delichon AS

Systems Architect & Senior Developer

Customer: Element Logic **Duration:** 5 years

Roles: Senior Systems Developer, Security Champion

Technologies: C#, Akka.NET, Blazor, REST, GraphQL, NHibernate, SQL, NUnit, Moq, Microsoft .NET Standard, ASP.NET, TeamCity,

Octopus Deploy, Git, Powershell, Kiuwan.

Responsibility: Senior developer on Element Logic's main product, eManager. Additionally, focuses on application security, and is the initiator and leader for Element Logic's Security Chapions Guild.

Customer: ABB

Role: Senior Systems Developer

Duration: 6 months

Technologies: Azure DevOps, Azure DB, Azure WebServices, Akka.NET, TypeScript, React JS, C#, Microsoft .NET Core, TFS, Git, Powershell.

01/2018 - 04/2019

Sopra Steria

Lead Software Engineer

Roles: In-house architect responsible for planning and QA of offers to customers. Senior developer for some customers.

Customers: Skatteetaten, Helsedirektoratet.

Technologies: C#, .Net, Episerver CMS, ASP.NET MVC, Microsoft

SQL Server, JavaScript, Jira, Confluence, TFS, Git.

03/2014 - 08/2017

CGI

Senior Web Developer

Roles: Team Leader, Scrum Master, Hands-on Architect. Customers: ASKO, Fellesforbundet, Tekna, PIA, Miljødirektoratet. Technologies: C#, inRiver PIM, Apptus eSales, Episerver CMS, Episerver Commerce, IdentityServer, T-SQL, NServiceBus, Jira, Confluence, jMeter, BlazeMeter, Angular.js, Knockout.js.

Making Waves, Senior Systems Consultant Creuna, Consultant / Systems Developer Ocelluz, Systems Developer & Project Manager Anders Nordby Konsulenttjenester Ajilon, Consultant